var jsonMedical = `{
  "id": 105,
  "title": "Medical",
  "clues": [{
      "id": 6000,
      "answer": "Cushing's disease",
      "question": "A disease caused by a tumor on the pituatary gland",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6001,
      "answer": "Vitamin K",
      "question": "The vitamin essential to aid in blood clotting",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6002,
      "answer": "Colic",
      "question": "The general term for pain in the abdomen",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6003,
      "answer": "100",
      "question": "The average temperature of a horse in degrees",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6004,
      "answer": "Chestnut",
      "question": "A term that describes a horny growth on the inside of a horse's leg",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6005,
      "answer": "Arthritis",
      "question": "The scientific name for joint inflammation",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6006,
      "answer": "Vitamin D",
      "question": "Vitamin that is obtained by most horses through sunshine and sun-cured hay",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6007,
      "answer": "Pigeon toed",
      "question": "Term for the conformational defect in which the hoofs of the front legs of the horse point in rather than straight ahead",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6008,
      "answer": "Vitamin D",
      "question": "Rickets occurs only in young animals and can be caused by a deficiency of this vitamin",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6009,
      "answer": "Iron",
      "question": "Deficiency of this trace mineral can cause anemia",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6010,
      "answer": "Antidote",
      "question": "The remedy to counteract a poison",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6011,
      "answer": "Calcium",
      "question": "The mineral that is the partner to phosphorus and is important for healthy bones and teeth",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6012,
      "answer": "Paint",
      "question": "Lethal white foal syndrome is associated with this breed of horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6013,
      "answer": "Vitamin A",
      "question": "This fat-soluble vitamin is needed for vision",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6014,
      "answer": "Protein",
      "question": "Soybean meal and canola meal are the best sources of this type of basic nutrient",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6015,
      "answer": "Thrush",
      "question": "The infection of the frog area of the foot caused by anaerobic microorganisms and has a foul, blackish discharge",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6016,
      "answer": "Overfeeding",
      "question": "In the United States, nutritional problems in horses are more likely associated with which of these â€“ overfeeding or underfeeding?",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6017,
      "answer": "Iodine",
      "question": "Deficiency of this trace mineral may cause a goiter",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6018,
      "answer": "Amino acids",
      "question": "Often referred as the building blocks of the body",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6019,
      "answer": "Opossum",
      "question": "This animal is the primary host of Equine Protozoal Myeloencephalitis",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6020,
      "answer": "Parrot mouth",
      "question": "Term for a horse that has an extreme overbite",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6021,
      "answer": "Gray",
      "question": "A tumor of pigment forming cells called a melanoma is most common in this color horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 6022,
      "answer": "Swayback",
      "question": "A concave or sagging back indicative of weakness in the back",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 105,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    }
  ]
}`;
